# **Philip Benn**

# Oakland, CA 94611 | 310-403-1826 | philipaldenbenn@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/philip-benn-5977142

# Designer/Professor/Generative AI Dev

Designer, professor, and developer with a background in 3D production for product rendering and animation. Expert knowledge of generative ai. Excellent written and verbal communication skills and problem-solving abilities. An outgoing and personable team member.

## **Areas of Expertise**

**3D Production and Product Rendering:** Adobe Creative Suite, Cinema4D, Maya, Rhino, Nuke, Blender | **Generative AI:** Stable Diffusion, ComfyUI, Automatic1111 | **Web Development:** VSCode, Python, JAMstack web development architecture

#### Links

Portfolio: https://benn-portfolio.vercel.com

#### Education

Master of Fine Arts (MFA), Design Technology
San Francisco Art Institute
Bachelor of Arts (BA), English Literature
Virginia Commonwealth University

## **Experience**

Synthemo: synthemo.com 2024 – Current

**Art Director and Developer** 

Design and development full stack web app for Synthemo.com and the node-based generative ai app Fluxion.

Hopeflo: hopeflo.org 2024 – Current

**Art Director and Developer** 

Design and development of full stack web app for Hopeflo.org and the node-based generative ai app Fluxion.

California College of Art: portal.cca.edu/people/pbenn

Adjunct Faculty, MFA Design 2015 – Current

Teach motion studio and MFA exhibition courses.

XYZ Studios: wearexyz.com

Adjunct Faculty, MFA Design 2015 – Current

Taught motion studio and MFA exhibition courses.

NovelSpace/Elysium System: novelspace-website-novel-space-team.vercel.app 2023

**Art Director and Developer** 

Designed and Developed full stack web apps integrating LLMs, Stable Diffusion Txt2img ML models.

RESUME IS CONTINUED ON FOLLOWING PAGE...

Logitech 2019 – 2023

## **Staff lead Visual Designer**

Created and executed workflows for marketing assets. Worked with Engineering, Industrial Designers, Product Managers.

- Served as a project lead of four years of product launches for the mobility team.
- Created 3D Rendering, 2D Design Visualization.
- Performed CAD data conversion into DCC renderable assets.
- Created photorealistic imagery for Logitech website, in-store POS, packaging, and partner websites.

Schawk 2017 – 2018

#### Staff 3D Technical Director

Created digital image assets for Apple product refresh and launch events.

• Executed Workflow for digital asset production of high-resolution, photorealistic imagery for product launches and in-store POS.

Nvidia 2014 – 2017

### **Staff 3D Technical Director**

Created digital image assets for Nvidia events and product launches.

- Researched and developed off-line and real-time GPU rendering pipelines.
- Performed product testing for Nvidia's in-house GPU progressive and programmable renderer.
- Created workflows for CAD data conversion into DCC renderable assets.

## **Additional Relevant Experience**

Prologue Films, Technical Director | Visual Designer | Staff | Contractor
Eveo
Hydraulx
Atmospheric
R/GA

School of Visual Arts, Computer Art Professor Taught courses in 3D computer graphics.

Virginia Commonwealth University, Design Department Professor

Taught courses in computer graphics and animation.